export const questionAndAnswers = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Aman",
    questionedBy: "Aman Sen",
    question: "What is the famous food of Agra?",
    answer: "Petha is the famous sweet of Agra",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: true,
    time: "22:45:00 PM",
    date: "1 Jan 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Nikhil",
    questionedBy: "Amartya",
    question: "What color is the sky?",
    answer:
      "The sky is of color blue.The color is blue because The Raman Effect",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: true,
    time: "16:20:00 PM",
    date: "10 July 2023",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Nitish",
    questionedBy: "Abhishek",
    question: "When did the world war start?",
    answer: "The world war 1 started in 1914",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:23:00 AM",
    date: "6 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Shubham",
    questionedBy: "Ankit",
    question: 'Which animal is known as the "Ship of the Desert"?',
    answer: "Camel",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "23:22:00 PM",
    date: "3 May 2019",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Abhishek",
    questionedBy: "Amartya",
    question: "How many consonants are there in the English alphabet?",
    answer: "21 Consonants",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "11:55:04 AM",
    date: "22 June 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Amartya",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: "Who designed the National Flag of India?",
    answer: "Pingali Venkayya",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "12:22:00 PM",
    date: "19 Dec 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answeredBy: "Shivani",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question: "Who founded the Banaras Hindu University?",
    answer: "Madan Mohan Malviya",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "7:00:00 AM",
    date: "7 July 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answeredBy: "Divya",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question:
      "Which satelite was launched recently under lunar exploring mission by ISRO?",
    answer: "Chandrayan 3 on 14 july 2023",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "13:13:00 PM",
    date: "30 June 2023",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answeredBy: "Utkarsh",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question: "Who gave the slogan “Inquilab Zindabad”?",
    answer: "Bhagat Singh",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:00:00 AM",
    date: "21 Dec 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answeredBy: "Sourabh",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Who built 'Purana Quila' in Delhi?",
    answer: "Sher Shah suri",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "14:11:00 PM",
    date: "11 October 2018",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answeredBy: "Astha",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "Which is the oldest form of composition of Hindustani Vocal Music?",
    answer: "Dhrupad",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:40:10 AM",
    date: "1 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answeredBy: "Ankit",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: `Who is known as "Father of Indian Cinema"`,
    answer: " Dada Sheb Phalke",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "3:23:00 AM",
    date: "27 July 2023",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answeredBy: "Astha",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question:
      "Which substances are found in food that help our body to grow and develop?",
    answer: "Nutrients ",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:05:00 AM",
    date: "15 Dec 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    answeredBy: "Ankit",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Which ingredients can be found in many Indian recipes?",
    answer: "Curry",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:11:00 AM",
    date: "30 April 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Jayant",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "Movie music in India is made for the Indian movie industry. What is the Indian movie industry called?",
    answer: "Bollywood",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "22:12:10 PM",
    date: "9 August 2021",
  },
];

export const questionLists = [
  {
    id: "1",
    questionedBy: "Kamal rastogi",
    question: "Which is the tallest mountain in the world?",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    questionedBy: "Rahul Kumar",
    question: "Rainbow consist of how many colours?",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    questionedBy: "Jatin Rawat",
    question: "Which is the largest plateau in the world?",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    questionedBy: "Jatin Rawat",
    question: "Who designed the National Flag of India?",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    questionedBy: "Rahul Kumar",
    question: "Difference between strees and strain?",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    questionedBy: "Abhishek",
    question: "How many hours are there in a day?",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    questionedBy: "Amartya",
    question: "What color is the sky?",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    questionedBy: "Shubham",
    question: "How many days are there in a year?",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question:
      "How many vowels are there in the English alphabet and name them?",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    questionedBy: "Astha",
    question: 'Which animal is known as the "Ship of the Desert"?',
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question: "Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    questionedBy: "Amartya",
    question: "When did the world war start?",
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    questionedBy: "Aman Sen",
    question: "What is the famous food of Agra?",
  },
];

export const history = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Shivani",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question: "Who founded the Banaras Hindu University?",
    answer: "Madan Mohan Malviya",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "7:00:00 AM",
    date: "7 July 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Divya",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question:
      "Who was the founder and editor of the famous newspaper 'Kesari' during the national struggle?",
    answer: "Lokmanya Tilak",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "13:13:00 PM",
    date: "30 June 2023",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Utkarsh",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question: "Who gave the slogan “Inquilab Zindabad”?",
    answer: "Bhagat Singh",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:00:00 AM",
    date: "21 Dec 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Sourabh",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Who built 'Purana Quila' in Delhi?",
    answer: "Sher Shah suri",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "14:11:00 PM",
    date: "11 October 2018",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Astha",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "From which station was the rail journey started in India for the first time?",
    answer: " In 1853 - Bombay (Mumbai)",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:40:10 AM",
    date: "1 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Ankit",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: "Buddha was related to which dynasty?",
    answer: "Shakya",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "3:23:00 AM",
    date: "27 July 2023",
  },
];

export const science = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Pushpa",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question:
      "Which satelite was launched recently under lunar exploring mission by ISRO?",
    answer: "Chandrayan 3 on 14 july 2023",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "7:00:00 AM",
    date: "7 July 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Shivam",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question: "Who is known as the father of Indian space program?",
    answer: "Vikrama sarabhai",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "19:13:00 PM",
    date: "12 June 2023",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Anuradha",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question: "Which metal is used in the making of microchips?",
    answer: "Silicon",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:05:00 AM",
    date: "12 Dec 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Abhishek",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Which gases cause acid rain?",
    answer: "Sulphur dioxide, Nitrogen oxide",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:11:00 PM",
    date: "3 October 2020",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Avilash",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: "Which is the most abundant gas in the earth's atmosphere?",
    answer: "Nitrogen (78.08%)",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "9:12:10 AM",
    date: "14 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Kishore",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "Which gas is safe and an effective extinguisher for all confined fires?",
    answer: "Carbon dioxide",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:21:00 AM",
    date: "20 June 2022",
  },
];

export const movies = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Akanksha",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question: "Who invented the cinematograph?",
    answer: " Lumiere Brothers",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "7:00:00 AM",
    date: "7 July 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Khushboo",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question: `Who is known as "Father of Indian Cinema"`,
    answer: " Dada Sheb Phalke",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "19:13:00 PM",
    date: "1 June 2023",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Himanshu",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question:
      "Which award honoured to Amitabh Bachchan from the President Ram Nath Kovind at the Rashtrapati Bhavan?",
    answer: "Dadasaheb Phalke award",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:05:00 AM",
    date: "11 Dec 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Ankita",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Where was the first cinema demonstrated in India?",
    answer: "Bombay (Now Mumbai) at Watkins Hotel",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:11:00 PM",
    date: "30 October 2020",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Nikhil",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: "Which was the first India's talkie film?",
    answer: "Alam Ara",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "22:12:10 PM",
    date: "1 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Aakash",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "Which movie was the first made indigenous, coloured film of India?",
    answer: "Kisan Kanya",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:21:00 AM",
    date: "2 April 2021",
  },
];

export const health = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Sujata",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question:
      "In what year was the World Health Organization (WHO) established?",
    answer: "1945",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "17:20:00 PM",
    date: "16 July 2019",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Ankita",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question: "What is the leading cause of death worldwide?",
    answer: "Heart disease",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: true,
    time: "9:13:00 AM",
    date: "11 June 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Astha",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question:
      "Which substances are found in food that help our body to grow and develop?",
    answer: "Nutrients ",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:05:00 AM",
    date: "15 Dec 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Samridhhi",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Which is responsible for the sweetness of milk?",
    answer: "Lactose",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:11:00 AM",
    date: "30 October 2020",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Anjali",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: "What is the chemical name of Vitamin B9?",
    answer: "Folic acid",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: true,
    time: "22:12:10 PM",
    date: "19 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Priyadarshi",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "What is the name of the disease in man arising out of Vitamin B1 deficiency?",
    answer: "Beri beri",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:21:00 AM",
    date: "20 April 2022",
  },
];

export const cooking = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Abhishek",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question: "What is often the first step in most baking recipes?",
    answer: "Preheating oven",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:20:00 PM",
    date: "19 May 2019",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Amartya",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question:
      "What is the culinary term for improving the presentation of a dish by decorating with ingredients?",
    answer: "Garnish",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: true,
    time: "19:13:00 PM",
    date: "11 September 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Aman",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question: "What is the best way to make onions taste sweeter?",
    answer: "Caramelise",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "14:05:00 AM",
    date: "16 November 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Ankit",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question: "Which ingredients can be found in many Indian recipes?",
    answer: "Curry",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:11:00 AM",
    date: "30 April 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Nikhil",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "What's the best way to improve knife skills without taking a course?",
    answer:
      "Look up an onion chopping tutorial on YouTube and practice with a full bag of yellow onions.",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: true,
    time: "22:12:10 PM",
    date: "19 March 2020",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Nitish",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question: "What's the best way to melt chocolate?",
    answer:
      "Chop it (or use chips) and melt in the microwave for 30 second intervals, stirring each time until completely smooth.",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:21:00 AM",
    date: "20 May 2021",
  },
];

export const music = [
  {
    id: 1,
    answeredBy: "Manish",
    questionedBy: "Divya",
    question:
      "Which is the oldest form of composition of Hindustani Vocal Music?",
    answer: "Dhrupad",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "17:20:00 PM",
    date: "15 July 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answeredBy: "Aman",
    questionedBy: "Shivani",
    question: "Which is a wind instrument?",
    answer: "Shehnai",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "9:13:00 AM",
    date: "12 June 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answeredBy: "Aniket",
    questionedBy: "Amit",
    question: "Which stringed instrument has the most number of strings?",
    answer: "Sitar",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "18:05:00 AM",
    date: "14 Dec 2019",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answeredBy: "Agam",
    questionedBy: "Shivam",
    question:
      "Hindustani classical music is broken into groups of notes. What is that groups of notes be called?",
    answer: "Raaga",
    upvote: false,
    downvote: false,
    time: "8:11:00 AM",
    date: "3 October 2022",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answeredBy: "Jayant",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "Movie music in India is made for the Indian movie industry. What is the Indian movie industry called?",
    answer: "Bollywood",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "22:12:10 PM",
    date: "9 August 2021",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answeredBy: "Ashish",
    questionedBy: "Nitish",
    question:
      "With which song did Lata Mangeshkar do her first Hindi playback ?",
    answer: "Pa Lagoon Kar Jori Re Shyam",
    upvote: true,
    downvote: false,
    time: "10:21:00 AM",
    date: "20 May 2021",
  },
];
